Guide to the George Dudley Seymour Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Oversize, Series VII
  - Proclamations and certificates
    - George Dudley Seymour
      - Diplomas, honorary degress, and centennial documents of George Washington University (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 18 July 1780
        - Printed announcement of tax assessment on the town of Shutesbury, Massachusetts, (95 pounds), signed by Henry Gardner, state treasurer and receiver general. (Box 118, Folder 1)
      - 1 January 1842
        - "Printers' New Years' Address. West Brookfield, January 1, 1842." Printed poem. (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Architectural drawings (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - New Haven, Connecticut
      - Arch of Welcome (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Streets (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - South Coventry, Connecticut
      - Hale, Nathan--birthplace (Box 118, Folder 2)
      - Northampton house (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Patent certificates (Box 118, Folder 3)
    Seven (7) patent certificates, petitioned for and awarded to Edward Thomas Hughes of the firm of Hughes and Son, Patent Agents, London, England.
    See also: box 117
    - 1866 (#720) David Hand Wilcox of New Haven, Connecticut, for improvements in weighing scales. (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - 1869 (#1181) Oliver Fisher Winchester of New Haven, Connecticut, for "improvements in rifled firearms and ordinance and ammunition for the same." (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - 1871 (#985) Charles Tomlinson Shelton of New Haven, Connecticut, for improvements in driving whips. (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - 1872 (#4445) Nathan Adolphus Baldwin of New Haven, Connecticut, for improvements in machines for sewing boots and shoes. (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - 1875 (#394) Benjamin Silliman, Jr, of New Haven, Connecticut, and Horace Cornwall Wilcox of West Meriden, Connecticut, for "Improvements in treating certain metallic alloys for importing resonance thereto." (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - 1876 (#1827) Varnam Nash Taylor, William Henry Harvey, and Theodore Alden Curtis of Springfield, Massachusetts, for a new or improved Gas Light Extinguisher (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - 1880 (#590) Nathan Adolphas Baldwin of New Haven, Connecticut, for improvements in sewing machines. (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Indentures
  - Newspaper clippings and maps: Nathan Hale (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - 1776 Oct 12
      - New Hampshire [State] Gazette (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - 1841 Dec
      - Brother Jonathan, "The Switch-Tail Pacer," by John Neal, chapters II-IV (Box 118, Folder 4)
        See also: box 70, folder 1040
      - Miscellaneous and undated clippings and maps (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - "New Haven Losing Elms," New York DailyTribune, 1909 Apr 18 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - "Saloon Map of New Haven" [1911?] (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - "Outline-Plan-for Pine Rock Reservation" [Olmsted Brothers, architects], 1908 Mar 9 (Box 118, Folder 5)